{
    "subject": "resource/Mary_Poppins_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Walt_Disney",
    "human_readable": "Walt Disney produced the film Mary Poppins.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8882454633712769,
            "question": "Who produced the film Mary Poppins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.752937376499176,
            "question": "Which famous filmmaker produced Mary Poppins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7257546186447144,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Walt Disney."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7003906965255737,
            "question": "What year was the film Mary Poppins released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6922981142997742,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Walt Disney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6721582412719727,
            "question": "Who starred in the film Mary Poppins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.596792995929718,
            "question": "Walt Disney is known for producing what type of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5941066145896912,
            "question": "What genre is the film Mary Poppins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5221018195152283,
            "question": "Is Mary Poppins a live-action or animated film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.485895574092865,
            "question": "What makes Mary Poppins a popular and enduring film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Walt Disney produced the film Mary Poppins.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6971_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mary Poppins a live-action or animated film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6971_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Mary Poppins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6971_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Walt Disney is known for producing what type of films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6971_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6971_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Walt Disney produced the film Mary Poppins. The document with file path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6971/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt explicitly states that Walt Disney was the producer of the 1964 American musical fantasy comedy film Mary Poppins."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Mary Poppins is a 1964 American movie directed by Robert Stevenson and produced by Walt Disney,\" which supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}